mysubs.co.za 2012-09-20

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy policy**

We are committed to protecting your privacy, in accordance with the ECT Act. We uphold strict security procedures regarding storing, using and disclosing your personal information. For the purpose of this clause, "personal information" shall be defined as detailed in the Promotion of Access to Information Act 2 of 2000 (PAIA). The PAIA may be downloaded from: <http://www.polity.org.za/html/govdocs/legislation/2000/act2.pdf>

On the Dot may electronically collect, store and use the following personal information:

1\. Name and surname

2\. Birth date

3\. Gender

4\. Country of residence

5\. Closest city

6\. Non-personal browsing habits and click patterns

7\. Email address

8\. IP address

9\. ID number/passport number

10\. Telephone number

  The personal information that we collect from you is either collected electronically by using “cookies” as detailed in the terms and conditions below or provided by the user voluntarily.

Personal information is requested in order to:

1\. enable us to discharge our obligations towards you and to enforce our rights against you;

2\. greet you when you access and log onto the On the Dot website;

3\. subject to your consent, inform you about facts relating to your access to and use of the On the Dot website;

4\. subject to your consent, inform you about competitions and special offers from On the Dot or any of our affiliates or contractors;

5\. compile non-personal information about browsing habits, click patterns and access to the On the Dot website;

6\. verify your identity when transacting with On the Dot;

7\. ensure that you receive any goods purchased on the On the Dot website;

8\. be incorporated into a database used for marketing purposes.

On the Dot may collect, maintain, save, compile, share, disclose and sell any information collected from you, subject to the following provisions:

1\. On the Dot shall not disclose your personal information without your consent;

2\. On the Dot shall only disclose information without your consent through due legal process;

3\. On the Dot may compile, use and share any information that does not relate to any specific individual;

4\. On the Dot owns and retains all rights to non-personal statistical information collected and compiled by the company.

You may elect not to receive any communication from On the Dot or any of our affiliates.  

Contact us if you have reason to believe that On the Dot has failed to adhere to the privacy policy as set out above.  

We automatically send a tiny text file called a "cookie" to your computer's hard disc drive when you visit the website. A cookie is a piece of information that your computer shows to our server when you log onto the website. [Note: There is not a cookie that will remember the user if he/she terminates the session. The user has to login each time.]  

Cookies enable the website to recognise information you have given to us previously, and allow you to maintain lightboxes, use a shopping cart and conclude purchase agreements in respect of goods.  

Our use of the cookie is limited to your activities on the website and does not have any other effect on your computer or your other activities on the Internet.  

The user may determine cookie use independently through the browser settings.
